[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 14, "question": "Why are you here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 15, "answer": "Thank you for having me, by the way.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 19, "question": "What do you want to achieve with this interview?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 20, "answer": "I think you should tell them a little of the backstory about how we first met.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 107, "question": "Were you unprofessional?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 108, "answer": "Well, yes, I was late a couple of days when we were just practicing, when it was just rehearsal.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 143, "question": "$1.8 million a day?", "question_pos_tagged": ["$", "CD", "CD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 144, "answer": "Doesn't mean I save any.", "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$1.8 million"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 145, "question": "You know what?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 146, "answer": "Whatever.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 162, "question": "What is the answer to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 163, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", ",", "WDT", "TO", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "MD", "VB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 169, "question": "But did you hear that that was the case?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "WDT", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "I heard threats of it, yes, which to me felt like OK, that could be real, it could be just -- you know, just an empty threat, I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", ":", "RB", ",", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 172, "question": "That your behavior then had to be moderated?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 173, "answer": "HEEN: Absolutely, because then it's now we're into commerce.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 177, "question": "Were there repeated warnings as they're trying to suggest to people?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 178, "answer": "There was one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBD", "CD", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", ":", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 179, "question": "But as you carried on behaving in this manner and it got into the papers, you would be in big trouble?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 180, "answer": "There was one, but it wasn't -- it wasn't delivered in a way that was -- that was a threat.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 192, "question": "Would it be fair to say you didn't heed that warning?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 193, "answer": "Well, my hernia didn't heed that warning.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 198, "question": "You're not going to blame your hernia for all this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 199, "answer": "No, no, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 241, "question": "And you base that healing plain on previous experience?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 242, "answer": "Well, yes, I mean I've been to -- you know, a veteran of these wars -- a veteran of the unspeakable at times.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "Which carries with -- and do you accept it carries responsibility?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "NNS", "IN", ":", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 256, "question": "ORGAN: Which are different?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 257, "answer": "Absolutely it does.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 261, "question": "Do you wish you hadn't gone down certain pathways in the last few months?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "RP", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 262, "answer": "I think it's a waste of time, because I can't change it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 273, "question": "What was that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 274, "answer": "When I said, guys, I don't want to be gone too long, I can't be gone too long, because I'm worried about the crew.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PDT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "Do you feel guilty about the impact this -- your particular situation has had on the rest of the crew?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", ":", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "Well, I feel guilty that the perception of it has been that I'm the guy to blame for all of it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 295, "question": "No one is trying to call -- in fact, we're live, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ":", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 296, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 335, "question": "Do you believe that there was a subliminal plot at CBS that they wanted to get rid of you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 336, "answer": "Wow.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CBS"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 337, "question": "You mean like a conspiracy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 338, "answer": "Possibly.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 360, "question": "Well, plus it begs the question, why didn't they just replace me after season seven when I was asking for a ton of dough and say, all right, well, no, we're going to do the show, but not with you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "CD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "VB", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 361, "answer": "Let me ask you a direct question --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 372, "question": "Are you under the influence right now of any substance?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 373, "answer": "No, nothing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "NN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 384, "question": "It looks pretty cool to me, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 385, "answer": "But you took a drug test to prove that you are currently completely drug free.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 392, "question": "Yesterday?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "aSentId": 393, "answer": "The day before.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "RB", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "VBG", ",", "NN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 400, "question": "When was the last time you took a drug?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 401, "answer": "I don't know because not being, you know, held hostage by AA anymore, I don't count my days because it puts such a premium on them and you run around with your days, going, oh god, how was your day, how was your day, boom, I lost my days.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":"], "qSentId": 402, "question": "And then it's like, where did my days go?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 403, "answer": "You said --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "Do you wish you never got on that step?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "There's a couple of things I wish I hadn't started.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 414, "question": "What about drugs and narcotics?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 415, "answer": "Drugs, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJR", "RB", ",", "RB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VBZ", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 421, "question": "Where you thought I may die?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 422, "answer": "Probably more subconsciously, not so much at the forefront of, you know, within the scenario or whatever's taking place.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ":", "NNP", ":", "."], "qSentId": 455, "question": "You know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 456, "answer": "So somebody (INAUDIBLE).", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 460, "question": "Little excited, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 461, "answer": "Well, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "RBR", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 479, "question": "That if -- you're on tender hooks with you all the time, that leading your life on the edge like this is a constant worry for family, for friends, for fans, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 480, "answer": "I just -- I wish people would shift that focus on to themselves and their own family and their own friends and just maybe spend a little more time on their home front.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 488, "question": "Are you a happy guy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 489, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", ":", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "VB", "PDT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 501, "question": "Is it as simple as that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 502, "answer": "Well, no, I -- as long as I subscribe to the beliefs of others that build these models that don't really leave any room for individuality or creativity or anything that like, you know, they say you've got to surrender and you've got to get rid of your resentments, sit in a room and like be all lame, you know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 535, "question": "How would you have reacted to the star of your number one family comedy, which is watched by families and liked by families, behaving off-screen in the way that you've been behaving?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CD", "NN", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "VBD", "IN", "NNS", ",", "VBG", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 536, "answer": "HEEN: Well, I mean -- if I was -- I'd first look at the writing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 539, "question": "And it's not -- I don't think it comes close to -- I think it eclipses some of the stuff I'm doing out there on my most epic nights, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RP", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "RBS", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 540, "answer": "And of course the irony is your character's not exactly a saint.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", ",", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 544, "question": "There's a certain brand alignment here, isn't there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 545, "answer": "Right, but it's OK to smoke cigars, just not cigarettes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 546, "question": "OK?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "aSentId": 547, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "VBG", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NN", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 554, "question": "Do you think there's a hypocrisy there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 555, "answer": "I think that they in some way think that they have some magic literary influence over me by perhaps writing things and then going, oh, my god, look how powerful we are, now he's doing it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 569, "question": "And what function do those goddesses perform?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "NN", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 570, "answer": "Gosh, they -- it's -- I mean, name it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 572, "question": "You have two girlfriends, basically?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 573, "answer": "I do, yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 575, "question": "The wedge?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 576, "answer": "The wedge, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 577, "question": "What's the wedge?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 578, "answer": "The wedge is a football term.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 596, "question": "How far do you feel that sense of responsibility, in terms of your personal behavior?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 597, "answer": "Well, now -- with some distance from it, I realize its value and I plan to maintain it and protect it like a precious gem for the rest of my days.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 598, "question": "Do you think you got out of control?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 599, "answer": "Well, yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 601, "question": "It's as bad as you've ever been?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 602, "answer": "I wouldn't say it was as bad.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["afternoon"]}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "CD", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "VBG", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 606, "question": "Which bender?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "JJR", "."], "aSentId": 607, "answer": "The one where you had five women coming to your house at 4:00 in the afternoon.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "."], "qSentId": 616, "question": "You do take cocaine, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VB", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 617, "answer": "Well, I used to.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "VBG", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 623, "question": "What would you have taken on that particular bender?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 624, "answer": "Well, I hadn't done any for a while, like seven hours, but I had this hernia thing that was popping out.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 640, "question": "When they're on the playground, with their friends, all the embarrassment that comes their way?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 641, "answer": "It's a shame.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 645, "question": "So you never -- you've never had any drugs in the house when your kids were around?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 646, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 650, "question": "But that's just common sense and courtesy, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 651, "answer": "It is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 659, "question": "If you're running a big network like CBS, are you entitled to say you broke the law, therefore you're in breech of your contract?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 660, "answer": "Well, it's only illegal if I admit to it.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CBS"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", ",", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 665, "question": "But you wouldn't deny taking loads of cocaine?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 666, "answer": "Well, no, of course not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 669, "question": "Isn't that a bit of a moot point?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 670, "answer": "No, I'm talking about some of the sources they put -- that's the basket they put all the eggs in.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 686, "question": "I'm on a pink cloud?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 687, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 691, "question": "Do you feel angry now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 692, "answer": "No, I feel more alive.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 697, "question": "You're physically fit?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 698, "answer": "Yeah, no, I was at my high school weight of like 160.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 705, "question": "Can you get insurance for movies and stuff because of what's been going on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "IN", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 706, "answer": "Nobody has said that they can't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 716, "question": "What did Mel say to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "NNP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 717, "answer": "He was just, you know, not calling for any advice, just like thought you might like to hear a friendly voice.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "RP", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 721, "question": "Sean Penn?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 722, "answer": "Sorry to out you, dude.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sean Penn"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 723, "question": "What did he say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 724, "answer": "He was happy to see me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 730, "question": "Do any of them do that to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 731, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", ":", "RB", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 733, "question": "Oh, you mean during the party or right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 734, "answer": "No, I mean, before -- obviously, now you're off the drugs and stuff.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 740, "question": "And when it's guy like that saying it to you, are they the people you listen to more than anybody on the outside?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "VBG", "PRP", "TO", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "JJR", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 741, "answer": "Yeah, because they know me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "POS", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 750, "question": "Because you're so competitive, that pressure when you're number one to stay number one, can that in itself drive you to go and seek release, to go and want to go and have a few days getting away from it all?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "IN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "CD", "TO", "VB", "NN", "CD", ",", "MD", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 751, "answer": "Of course, that's I'm sure one of the elements that might drive it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 766, "question": "HEEN: Right, you mean the whole store?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", ":", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 767, "answer": "Pretty much.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie"]}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 770, "question": "Gosh, where do we go from here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 771, "answer": "Only way is up, Charlie.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 781, "question": "Do you regret what happened on those two incidents?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 782, "answer": "Those are two incidents where the scoreboard doesn't lie.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 789, "question": "Have you ever hit a woman?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 790, "answer": "I have not, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 792, "question": "They're to be hugged and caressed, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 793, "answer": "A few people that are very close to you have expressed real concern.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 797, "question": "Who was that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 798, "answer": "Her initials are B.A. I'll give you that much.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "IN", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 804, "question": "You regret that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 805, "answer": "Yeah, she was attacking me, though, with a small fork, like a cocktail fork.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 810, "question": "Is there ever any defense?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 811, "answer": "You can't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNP", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 814, "question": "But you regret that incident?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 815, "answer": "Oh, God, yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 832, "question": "Stan, where did you go?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 833, "answer": "He loves you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "RB", "IN", "RB", "CC", ":", "CC", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 846, "question": "What would you say to Stan if he's watching this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 847, "answer": "Get back over here and -- and stop with your silliness.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Stan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 855, "question": "Have you talked to your father?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 856, "answer": "I have not, no.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 858, "question": "You haven't discussed it with him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 859, "answer": "No, I'm sure he'll hear something about it in one of these interviews.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 862, "question": "Do you not speak to him much?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 863, "answer": "No, I mean -- he's been out of the country, I think.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 869, "question": "Is your game plan to actually end up getting your job back?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "RP", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 870, "answer": "Well, I would love that, yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 882, "question": "Do you have it in you to be disciplined enough now to not fall by the wayside?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "JJ", "RB", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 883, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "VBG", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 888, "question": "Were you joking?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 889, "answer": "No, I was joking about being underpaid.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 895, "question": "Where's Dr. Drew when you need him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 896, "answer": "Funny enough, we have got a clip from Dr. Drew.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dr. Drew"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dr. Drew"]}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 902, "question": "What are his credentials?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 903, "answer": "Let's take a quick listen to Dr. Drew.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", ":", "VBP", "IN", ",", "NN", ",", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 917, "question": "What do you think when you hear that kind of professional?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 918, "answer": "I think you cannot -- you cannot -- come on, man, that's ridiculous.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 925, "question": "Have you seen it work for friends of yours?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 926, "answer": "Some, yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 956, "question": "What do you mean?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 957, "answer": "Millions of fans just want the show back on the air.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 958, "question": "What is is the way to make that happen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 959, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 961, "question": "What would you say if you did?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 962, "answer": "HEEN: I would say, OK, you've agreed to pay the crew four show.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 968, "question": "What would you then sign up to, in terms of personal behavior?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "RP", "TO", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 969, "answer": "I don't -- I guess I would have to play ball on some front.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 977, "question": "You know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 978, "answer": "You're quite sensitive underneath the brash exterior.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Chuck and Vanity Cards"]}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 981, "question": "Has any of this really upset you, properly upset you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "IN", "DT", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 982, "answer": "I was upset after being kind of picked on and the little bit -- the bad stuff by Chuck and Vanity Cards for eight years.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 992, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 993, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 998, "question": "Do you regret making the little -- what appeared to be an anti-Semitic dig at him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", ":", "WP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 999, "answer": "Yes, I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", ":", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 1004, "question": "Would you say sorry to him if you had the chance?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 1005, "answer": "HEEN: Of course I would.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ":"], "qSentId": 1009, "question": "What's your biggest regret of all this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 1010, "answer": "That --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "VBG", "RP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 1011, "question": "If you had to do it all over again, what would you do differently?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "IN", "RB", ",", "WDT", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 1012, "answer": "Again, we have to go back to those moments and bring back a souvenir.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CBS"]}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 1018, "question": "You find out that those that can't stand the heat around them -- they don't really have the guts to survive, you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "WDT", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 1019, "answer": "No one from CBS has called in in the last hour.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 1021, "question": "How much time do we have left?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 1022, "answer": "We gave them the opportunity.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 1028, "question": "You would do that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 1029, "answer": "Yeah, I don't have a job.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CD", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 1035, "question": "How do you hope it ends?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 1036, "answer": "I have a vision of us getting back on the air for season nine and then doing season ten.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 1043, "question": "Have you talked to any of them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 1044, "answer": "I have not, because I don't feel like there's any real support there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110228pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 1052, "question": "Do they feel you've let them down?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 1053, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]